http://www.acalplc.co.uk/site-services/privacy

Strategy
Differentiated productsCross-sellingAcquisitionsOperational investments
Markets
MedicalRenewable energyIndustrial & ConnectivityTransportation
At a Glance
Group Summary Presentation – November 2020Design & manufacturingCustom supply
For Entrepreneurs
Our acquisition growth storyWhich businesses fit with discoverIE?Selling your business to discoverIEHow we do dealsAcquisition case studies
Sens-Tech – Steve JayeVariohm – Graham PattisonCursor – Neale SuttonHobart Electronics – Gary Kriadis
Contact our acquisition team
Investors
Investment caseResults centrePresentationsShare priceFive year recordShareholder information
General meetingsInformation Document
Major shareholdersAnalyst coverageFinancial calendar
News centre
Press releasesRegulatory newsFeatured press coverageVideo library
Sustainability
Our approachAlignment to the UN Sustainable Development GoalsEnvironment
Terms of Reference
Audit and Risk CommitteeNomination CommitteeRemuneration Committee
Company policies
Whistle blowing policyAnti-bribery statementModern slavery statement
Strategy
Differentiated productsCross-sellingAcquisitionsOperational investments
Markets
MedicalRenewable energyIndustrial & ConnectivityTransportation
At a Glance
Group Summary Presentation – November 2020Design & manufacturingCustom supply
For Entrepreneurs
Our acquisition growth storyWhich businesses fit with discoverIE?Selling your business to discoverIEHow we do dealsAcquisition case studies
Sens-Tech – Steve JayeVariohm – Graham PattisonCursor – Neale SuttonHobart Electronics – Gary Kriadis
Contact our acquisition team
Investors
Investment caseResults centrePresentationsShare priceFive year recordShareholder information
General meetingsInformation Document
Major shareholdersAnalyst coverageFinancial calendar
News centre
Press releasesRegulatory newsFeatured press coverageVideo library
Sustainability
Our approachAlignment to the UN Sustainable Development GoalsEnvironment
Terms of Reference
Audit and Risk CommitteeNomination CommitteeRemuneration Committee
Company policies
Whistle blowing policyAnti-bribery statementModern slavery statement
Strategy
Differentiated productsCross-sellingAcquisitionsOperational investments
Markets
MedicalRenewable energyIndustrial & ConnectivityTransportation
At a Glance
Group Summary Presentation – November 2020Design & manufacturingCustom supply
For Entrepreneurs
Our acquisition growth storyWhich businesses fit with discoverIE?Selling your business to discoverIEHow we do dealsAcquisition case studies
Sens-Tech – Steve JayeVariohm – Graham PattisonCursor – Neale SuttonHobart Electronics – Gary Kriadis
Contact our acquisition team
Investors
Investment caseResults centrePresentationsShare priceFive year recordShareholder information
General meetingsInformation Document
Major shareholdersAnalyst coverageFinancial calendar
News centre
Press releasesRegulatory newsFeatured press coverageVideo library
Sustainability
Our approachAlignment to the UN Sustainable Development GoalsEnvironment
Terms of Reference
Audit and Risk CommitteeNomination CommitteeRemuneration Committee
Company policies
Whistle blowing policyAnti-bribery statementModern slavery statement
Strategy
Differentiated productsCross-sellingAcquisitionsOperational investments
Markets
MedicalRenewable energyIndustrial & ConnectivityTransportation
At a Glance
Group Summary Presentation – November 2020Design & manufacturingCustom supply
For Entrepreneurs
Our acquisition growth storyWhich businesses fit with discoverIE?Selling your business to discoverIEHow we do dealsAcquisition case studies
Sens-Tech – Steve JayeVariohm – Graham PattisonCursor – Neale SuttonHobart Electronics – Gary Kriadis
Contact our acquisition team
Investors
Investment caseResults centrePresentationsShare priceFive year recordShareholder information
General meetingsInformation Document
Major shareholdersAnalyst coverageFinancial calendar
News centre
Press releasesRegulatory newsFeatured press coverageVideo library
Sustainability
Our approachAlignment to the UN Sustainable Development GoalsEnvironment
Company policies
Whistle blowing policyAnti-bribery statementModern slavery statement
Covid-19 update
Contacts
Privacy
Who we are
The pages on the website (“the Website”) are published by Investis Limited (“Investis”), a company registered in England and Wales with company registration number 03930926, whose registered address is at 24 Fashion Street, London E1 6PX, on behalf of discoverIE Group plc, a company registered in England and Wales with company registration number 2008246, whose registered address is at 2 Chancellor Court, Occam Road, Guildford, Surrey GU2 7AH (“discoverIE”).
Investis and discoverIE respect your right to privacy and will process personal information you provide only in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 and other applicable privacy laws.
The information collected and how it is used
Investis will not collect any information about individuals, except where it is specifically and knowingly provided by them.
When you visit discoverIE’s Website, Investis’s web server collects some basic information such as your browser type, IP address, internet service provider’s domain name, which pages you accessed on the site, and when. Details of cookies that Investis uses on the Website can be found on the Cookie notice.
discoverIE and Investis use this information to provide you with and maintain the quality of the Website and to analyse the use of the Website in order to help guide improvements. Personally identifiable information is not automatically collected.
If you register for the alert service, you will need to provide your name and email address. This information will be held by Investis and may be accessed by Investis Corporate Communications PVT. Ltd (a subsidiary of Investis) from its premises in India for administration of the alert service. The information will not be used for any other purpose; it will be stored securely and will not be shared with third parties, except where you have given your consent or where Investis or discoverIE have a legal obligation to do so. Investis and discoverIE will only process the individual data that you provide for the intended purpose. By registering for the alerts, you consent to this use of your name and email address. Investis and discoverIE will take reasonable steps to ensure that the data held is accurate, relevant and not excessive for this purpose.
Investis and discoverIE take all reasonable steps to retain data only for the duration of the purpose for which it was obtained. When requested, Investis and/or discoverIE will delete personal information from current operational systems where it is no longer required. Investis and/or discoverIE may need to continue to hold some details about you after your relationship with Investis and/or discoverIE has ended, for example for legal and regulatory purposes.
Third-party use of information
Except as described above, neither Investis nor discoverIE will disclose, sell or rent your personal information to any third party unless you have consented to this. If you do consent but later change your mind, you may contact Investis or discoverIE (as appropriate) to ask for any such activity to stop.
However, if a third party acquires all (or substantially all) of Investis' or discoverIE's business and/or assets, Investis or discoverIE (as applicable) may disclose your personal information to that third party in connection with the acquisition. Investis or discoverIE may also disclose your personal information where required to do so by applicable law, by a governmental body or by a law enforcement agency.
Finally, Investis and/or discoverIE may also collect anonymised details about visitors to the Website for the purposes of aggregate statistics or reporting purposes. However, no single individual will be identifiable from the anonymised details collected for these purposes.
International transfers
Investis and/or discoverIE may transfer personal information that is collected from you to third-party data processors located in countries that are outside of the European Economic Area in connection with the above purposes. Please be aware that countries which are outside the European Economic Area may not offer the same level of data protection as the United Kingdom, although the collection, storage and use of your personal data will continue to be governed by this privacy policy.
Security
Whilst Investis and discoverIE take appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect the confidentiality and security of the personal information that you provide, no transmission over the Internet can ever be guaranteed secure. Consequently, please note that the security of any personal information that you transfer over the Internet to Investis and/or discoverIE cannot be guaranteed.
Your rights
You have the following rights:
the right to be provided with copies of personal information that Investis and/or discoverIE hold about you at any time, subject to a fee specified by law;
the right to ask Investis and/or discoverIE to update and correct any out-of-date or incorrect personal information held about you free of charge; and
the right to opt out of any marketing communications that Investis and/or discoverIE (or any third party to whom they have disclosed your personal information with your consent) may send you.
If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, please write to Investis or discoverIE (as appropriate) at the address specified above.
Third-party sites
The Website may contain links to other websites operated by third parties. Please note that this privacy policy applies only to the personal information that Investis and/or discoverIE collect through the Website and neither Investis nor discoverIE can be responsible for personal information that third parties may collect, store and use through their website. You should always read the privacy policy of each website you visit carefully.
Copyright © discoverIE Group plc 2020. All rights reserved.
Copyright © discoverIE 2017.All rights reserved.
